A Finding Aid to the Lillian and Frederick Kiesler Papers, circa 1910s-2003, bulk 1958-2000, in the Archives of American Art AAA.kieslill
Archives of American Art
- Lillian Kiesler papers, circa 1910s-2003; Series 1; (Box 1-39, 47-52, OV 53-55; 41.1 linear feet)
  - Papers Related to Frederick Kiesler, circa 1913-2003; 1.10
    - Writings and Notes, circa 1960s-1990s; 1.10.7
      - Untitled Theater Text (German), undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Various Notes, 1959-1965, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Various Notes and Scripts, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Various Writings, 1982-1995, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
        Includes originals.
      - Whistler, James McNeill, "Ten o'Clock", undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Printed Material, 1925-2001; 1.10.8
      Printed materials contain catalogs, magazine articles and newspaper clippings about Frederick Kiesler, pamphlets, monographs, posters, and invitations for Kiesler's exhibitions as well as exhibitions of his colleagues. Additional materials can be found in Exhibition Files, 1924-1992, undated (Subseries 2.4) and Printed Material, 1926-1966, undated (Subseries 2.7) in the Frederick Kiesler Papers, 1923-1992 (Series 2). Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material. Monographs are arranged alphabetically by the author's last name or title.
      - Catalogs and Journals, 1925-1968 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Catalogs and Journals, 1969-1982 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Catalogs and Journals, 1984, 1986, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Catalogs and Journals, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Catalogs and Journals (photocopies), 1990s, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Catalogs and Journals, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Magazines, 1934-1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Magazines, 1948-1966 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
      - Magazines, 1969-1984 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Magazines, 1987-1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        Oversized material housed in Box 49, Folder 11.
      - Magazines, 1996-2001, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Magazines (in Czech), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Magazines and Monographs (photocopies), 1943-2001 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Monographs (Box 25)
        - Abstraction création art non figuratif, 1933-1934 (Box 25, Folder 11)
        - Architectur Aus Österreich 1896-1996. Munich: Prestel (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Auflage, Zweite. Griechische Bildwerke in Rom, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 13)
          Inscribed, 1957.
        - Barron, Stephanie. Exiles and Emigrés: The Flight of European Artists from Hitler. Los Angeles: Los Angeles County Museum, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
          See also Box 21, Folders 26-27.
        - Blake, William. Songs of Experience. (Inscribed, 1952) and Songs of Innocence. New York: United Book Guild, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
        - The Book of the Shrine. (German), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 16)
          Oversized materials housed in OV 54.
        - Dessauce, Marc. Machinations: Essai sur Frederick Kiesler, L'historie de L'architecture Modern aux États-Unis et Marcel Duchamp, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - Eidelberg, Martin, ed. Design 1935-1965: What Modern Was. New York: Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
        - El Retablo de Maefe Pedro. London: J and W Chester, Ltd., 1923 (Box 25, Folder 19)
          Musical score.
        - Grande, John K. Art and Environment. Toronto: The Friendly Chameleon, Ltd., 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
        - Janis, Harriet and Sidney. Picasso: The Recent Years 1939-1946. New York: Doubleday and Co., Inc. (Box 25, Folder 251)
      - Monographs (Box 26)
        - Kiesler, Frederick. Inside the Endless House. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - McDarrah, Fred. The Artist's World in Pictures. New York: E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - Milhaud, Darius. The Play of Robin and Marion. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1951 (Box 26, Folder 3)
          Cover of vocal score designed by Frederick Kiesler.
        - Neagoe, Peter. Winning a wife and other stories. New York: Coward-McCann, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 4)
          Inscribed by author, 1944.
        - Satie, Erik. Le Piege de Meduse, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
          Music score.
        - The Shrine of the Book: A Biography, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - The Tiger's Eye, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 7)
          Two copies.
      - Newspaper Articles, 1958-2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Pamphlets, Invitations, and Postcards, 1964-1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Pamphlets, Invitations, and Postcards, 1997-2001, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Posters, 1967, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Printed Material, Magazines, "Bomb" magazine, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 11)
        Oversized material from Box 25, Folder 7.
      - Catalogs and Journals, "Cahiers d'Art", 1947 (Box OV 54)
        Oversized material from Box 24, Folder 30.
      - Magazines, Life Article on Modern Art, 1948 (Box OV 54)
        Oversized material from Box 25, Folders 4-5.
      - Magazines, Miscellaneous Articles, 1955, 1964 (Box OV 54)
      - Monographs, The Book of the Shrine (German), 1992 (Box OV 54)
        Oversized materials from Box 25, Folder 16.
      - Monographs, The Shrine of the Book: A Biography, 1998-1999 (Box OV 54)
        Oversized materials from Box 26, Folder 6.
      - Posters, 1967, 1998 (Box OV 54)
        Oversized material from Box 26, Folder 11.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1930s-2000; 1.10.9
      Photographic material includes photographs and color snapshots, contact sheets, negatives, and slides of artwork. Subject matter includes Lillian Kiesler with museum officials and in the Frederick Kiesler Archives storage facilities, Frederick Kiesler's drawings and sculptures, exhibitions, Frederick Kiesler at work, and slides and index cards from a lecture by Lillian Kiesler. Additional photographs of artwork can be found in Photographic Material, undated (Subseries 2.8) in the Frederick Kiesler Papers, 1923-1992 (Series 2); additional family and friends photographs as well as portraits can be found in Photographic Material, circa 1920s-2000 (Subseries 1.13) in the Lillian Kiesler Papers, circa 1910s-2003 (Series 1).
      - Artwork, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - New York Storage, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Philadelphia Museum, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
        Includes slides.
      - Storage Move, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
      - Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1931, 1942, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Contact Sheets and Negatives, circa 1960s, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Contact Sheets and Negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 2-6)
      - Contact Sheets and Photocopies of Photographs, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Slides, Artwork, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Slides and Index Cards, Lillian Kiesler's Slide Lecture about Frederick Kiesler, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
        Slides removed and housed in Box 49, Folder 15.
      - Transparencies and Negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Slides for Lillian Kiesler's Slide Lecture about Frederick Kiesler, undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
        Slides from Box 27, Folder 9.
    - Sound and Video Recordings, circa 1976-2003; 1.10.10
      Sound and video recordings are of lectures and interviews given by Lillian Kiesler and others about Frederick Kiesler and his work. Of interest are the recordings of Lillian Kielser's 1976 interview for "Music for the New Age" which includes a portion of tape from a 1965 interview with Frederick Kiesler; Frederick Kiesler's dialogue with Leo Castelli; and Lillian Kiesler interviewing Richard Kamler about Frederick Kiesler. Recordings are on 20 sound cassettes, 8 sound tape reels (1/4"), and 4 videocassettes (2 Betacam SP, 2 VHS). Transcripts for some interviews may be found in Interviews, circa 1962-2001 (Sub-subseries 1.10.6). It is arranged alphabetically by type of material, then subject.
      - Sound Cassettes, (Housed in shoebox) (Box 27, Folder 20)
        - Leo Castelli and Frederick Kiesler, undated; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Maryette Charlton, Gertrude Barnstone, and Lillian Kiesler on Frederick Kiesler, Radio Houston Interview, undated; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Maryette Charlton, Gertrude Barnstone, and Lillian Kiesler on Frederick Kiesler, KP and J Radio Station Interview, Houston, Texas, undated; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Interview with Richard Kamler conducted by Lillian Kiesler, 1979; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Efram Kiesler, 1978; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Interview with Lillian Kiesler and Lisa Phillips regarding the "Frederick Kiesler" Exhibition, Whitney Museum, 1989; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Lecture by Lillian Kiesler entitled "Frederick Kiesler, His Time and Space," Cooper Union, 1985; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Lecture by Lillian Kiesler entitled "Frederick Kiesler, His Time and Space," Iowa University Museum of Art, 1985; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Lecture by Frederick Kiesler, University of Iowa, 1985; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Lillian Kiesler Discussing Frederick Kiesler, 1989; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Lecture by Lillian Kiesler on Frederick Kiesler, Cooper Union, 1983; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
        - Varese-Meredith and Kiesler (1961), 2003; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 27)
      - "Endless House," Christopher Hermann, 1995; 2 Videocassettes (BetacamSP) (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - "Music for the New Age," Interview with Lillian Kiesler for WUHY-FM Philadelphia, 1976; 6 sound tape reels (Box 28, Folder 2)
        See also Box 22, 32.
      - "Round and About the Guggenheim," Radio Program involving Lillian Kiesler, 1976; 1 sound tape reels (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - "Us, You, Me", undated; 1 sound tape reels (Box 28, Folder 4)
        See also Box 22, Folder 20.
      - "Endless House," Christopher Hermann, 1995; 1 videocassettes: VHS (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Spanish Television Coverage of Frederick Kiesler Exhibition at Instituto Valenciano d'Arte Moderno, 1997; 1 videocassettes: VHS (Box 28, Folder 6)
        See also Box 22, Folders 9-10.
  - Papers of and Related to Hans Hofmann, 1932-2000, undated; 1.11
    The bulk of the material in the Papers of and Related to Hans Hofmann were created or compiled by Lillian Kiesler and document Hofmann's career and legacy. However, some material found here are the papers of Hofmann and the Hans Hofmann School of Fine Arts. Found is biographical material, correspondence, exhibition files, records of and related to the Hans Hofmann School of Fine Arts, interviews and lectures, writings and artwork, printed material, photographic material, and audio recordings. The Papers of and Related to Hans Hofmann are arranged into ten sub-subseries, each described in more detail in the sub-subseries description.
    - Biographical Material, undated; 1.11.1
      Biographical material includes a narrative curriculum vitae and a transcribed birth certificate. It is arranged alphabetically by subject.
      - Birth Certificate, Johann Georg Albert Hofmann, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, circa 1937-2000; 1.11.2
      Correspondence includes letters to and from Lillian Kiesler related to Hans Hofmann's artwork and estate, as well as some letters written by Hans Hofmann, to Lillian Kiesler and Alice Hodges describing his artwork, life in Provincetown and issues with the Hans Hofmann School of Fine Arts. Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject.
      - Business, 1941-1942, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Business, Acordia Insurance, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Business, Lillian Kiesler, 1966-1998, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Business, Jason McCoy Inc., Hans Hofmann Artwork Purchased, 1993-2000, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Christmas Cards to Lillian Kiesler and Alice Hodges, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Letters of Recommendation from Hans Hofmann, 1937, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Letters to Alice Hodges, 1938-1956, 1963-1964, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Letters to Hans Hofmann and Miz, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Letters to Lillian Kiesler, 1938-1964, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Letters to Lillian Kiesler and Alice Hodges, 1938-1949, 1953, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Transcription of Letters from Hans Hofmann, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition Files, 1960-1999; 1.11.3
      The bulk of the Exhibition Files are from posthumous exhibitions of Hans Hofmann's works and includes correspondence, press releases, clippings, exhibition catalogs, and loan agreements. It is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
      - Biennale Venezia, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Boston University Art Gallery, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Hirshhorn Museum, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1979, 1983, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1963, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - The Hans Hofmann School of Fine Arts, 1932-1958, undated; 1.11.4
      Found are class brochures, printed material, letterhead, and some correspondence from The Hans Hofmann School of Fine Arts. It also includes three boxes of student files on index cards. It is arranged alphabetically by subject.
      - The Hans Hofmann School of Fine Arts, 1938-1952, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Student Card Files, 1932-1958 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
        Three boxes.
    - Interviews and Lectures, circa 1983-2000, undated; 1.11.5
      The bulk of materials are transcripts, notes, and manuscripts of speeches, interviews, readings, and lectures given by Lillian Kiesler about Hans Hofmann. Also found are typed and handwritten lectures given by Hofmann and the transcript of Hofmann's 1941 address to the American Abstract Artists. It is arranged alphabetically by type of material.
      - Address, Hans Hofmann to American Abstract Artists' Exhibition (February 16, 1941), undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Interview, Lillian Kiesler and Ellen Landau (1989) (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Interview, Lillian Kiesler and Tina Dickey (1991), 1991-2000 (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
      - Interview, Lillian Kiesler and George McNeil (1991) (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Lectures, Hans Hofmann, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Lectures, Lillian Kiesler, circa 1983 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Lectures, Lillian Kiesler, Metropolitan Museum of Art, Index Cards, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - "Letters from Hans Hofmann, A Reading by Lillian Kiesler", University of Iowa, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
        See also Box 39, Folder 4.
      - "Letters from Hans Hofmann, A Reading by Lillian Kiesler", Whitney Museum of American Art, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Speech by Hans Hofmann, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Writings and Artwork, 1936-1950, 1963-2000, undated; 1.11.6
      Writings and artwork contains writings by and about Hans Hofmann and other writings, notes, drawings, Chinese calligraphy, and miscellany. Of note is a letter from an unidentified author (Lillian Kiesler?) describing Hofmann's critique of the artist's work in Provincetown in 1936 (located in Notes about Lee Krasner folder). Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
      - Chinese Pen and Ink Calligraphy Artwork, 1968, 1972, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
        Oversized material housed in OV 55.
      - Indian Currency, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Notes, 1974, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Notes about Lee Krasner, 1936, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Original Artwork, 1981, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Painting Descriptions by Lillian Kiesler, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Writings by Fritz Bultman, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Writings by Tina Dickey (proposed book) 1991-2000, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Writings by Cynthia Goodman, undated (Box 29, Folder 23-24)
      - Writings by Hans Hofmann, 1950, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Writings by Allan Kaprow, A Furniture Comedy for Hans Hofmann, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Writings by Valerie Komer, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Oversized Writings and Artwork, Chinese Pen and Ink Calligraphy, 1968, 1972, undated (Box OV 55)
        Oversized material from Box 29, Folder 15.
    - Printed Material, 1932-2000; 1.11.7
      Found among the printed material are exhibition catalogs, articles and monographs about Hans Hofmann, pamphlets, posters, and fliers announcing Hans Hofmann exhibits. The bulk of the magazine and newspaper articles are photocopies. Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material. Monographs are arranged alphabetically by author's last name or title.
      - Exhibition Catalogs, 1956-1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Exhibition Catalogs, 1981-1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Exhibition Catalogs, 1986-2000 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - "Look" article on Hans Hofmann, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Magazine and Newspaper Articles (photocopies), 1932, 1944-1966 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Magazine and Newspaper Articles (photocopies), 1964-1981, 1990-1994, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Monographs (Box 30)
        - Goodman, Cynthia. Hans Hofmann. New York: Whitney Museum of American Art, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Goodman, Cynthia. The Hans Hofmann School and Hofmann's Transmission of European Modernist Aesthetics to America. Ann Arbor: University Microfilms International, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - Greenberg, Clement. Hofmann. Paris: The Pocket Museum, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - Hofmann, Hans. Search for the Real. Andover: The Addison Gallery of American Art, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 10)
        - Partisan Review, June 1948 (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - Schnijf-taal ii (Written Language ii): Contemporary Poetry Collected by Simon Vinkenoog, circa 1964 (Box 30, Folder 12)
        - Seitz, William. Hans Hofmann. Garden City: Doubleday, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 13)
          Two copies; one hardback, one paperback.
        - Wight, Frederick. Hans Hofmann. Berkeley: University of California Press, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Pamphlets, Invitations, and Post Cards, 1944, 1949, 1957-1959, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Pamphlets, Invitations, and Postcards, 1944-1968 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Pamphlets, Invitations, and Postcards, 1979-1995, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - "Look" Article on Hans Hofmann, 1953 (Box OV 55)
        Oversized material from Box 30, Folder 4.
      - Pamphlets, Invitations, and Post Cards, 1944, 1949, 1957-1959, 1970 (Box OV 55)
        Oversized material from Box 30, Folder 15.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1950s-1999; 1.11.8
      Photographic material contains photographs of Hans Hofmann teaching and slides and transparencies of artwork. Of interest are photographs of Hofmann and his house in Provincetown taken by Wilfred Zogbaum and Tom Milius. Additional photographs of Hans Hofmann may be found in Photographic Material, circa 1920s-2000 (Subseries 1.13) in the Lillian Kiesler Papers, circa 1910s-2003 (Series 1). Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
      - Photographs of Hans Hofmann by Tom Milius, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Photographs of Hans Hofmann by Zogbaum, undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Photographs and Polaroids of Artwork, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Slides of Artwork, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Transparencies of Artwork, 1983, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Photographs of Hans Hofmann by Zogbaum, undated (Box OV 55)
        Oversized material from Box 30, Folder 19.
    - Sound Recordings, 1980-1991; 1.11.9
      Found are sound recordings of Lillian Kiesler's lectures and interviews about Hans Hofmann. Recordings are on 9 sound cassettes.
      - Lillian Kiesler Interviews, 1990-1991, undated; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Lillian Kiesler Lectures, 1980, 1983, 1990 undated; 6 Sound cassettes (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Papers of Alice Hodges, circa 1910s-1965; 1.12
    This subseries contains the personal papers of artist Alice Hodges and documents her personal life, artwork, and interests. Included are biographical material, correspondence, exhibition files, printed material, writings, miscellaneous files, artwork, and photographic material. The papers of Alice Hodges are arranged into eight sub-subseries; each is described in more detail in the sub-subseries description.
    - Biographical Material, circa 1928-1965; 1.12.1
      Biographical material contains ledgers, check stubs, estate records, driver's licenses, address books, addresses on index cards, records related to Hodges' death and last wishes, and other miscellaneous papers and notes. It is arranged alphabetically by subject.
      - Address Books and Calendars, 1930-circa 1963, undated (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
      - Addresses, Index Cards, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - American Women's Voluntary Services, 1942-1944, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Drivers Licenses and Vehicle Registration, 1928-1958 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Financial Records, 1955-1964, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Financial Records, 1961-1964 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Floyd R. Hodges Estate, 1939-1963, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Funeral Register, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Last Wishes, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous Papers and Notes, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Obituary, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Wallet Contents, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1935-1962; 1.12.2
      The correspondence is mostly personal in nature and includes letters from Hans Hofmann and Katherine Drier, as well as family members and friends. There are numerous postcards sent by Hodges and Lillian Kiesler from their trip to Europe in 1950. Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
      - Letters to Alice Hodges, 1935-1962 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Postcards from Alice Hodges' and Lillian Kiesler's Trip to Europe, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Files, 1957-1962, undated; 1.12.3
      Exhibition files contains material related to Hodges' showings in galleries and exhibits, including posters, announcements, catalogs, press releases, photographs of artwork, and correspondence. Folders are arranged alphabetically by exhibition.
      - Art U.S.A. (1958) (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - James Gallery, 1957-1962, undated (Box 32, Folder 7-8)
      - Kootz Gallery, Stable Gallery, Downtown Community School, 1950, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Luks Class, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - James Gallery Posters, 1957-1962, undated (Box OV 53)
        Oversized material from Box 32, Folders 7-8.
    - Printed Material, 1928-1964, undated; 1.12.4
      Included are newspaper clippings, exhibition catalogs and announcements, postcards, greeting cards, and magazine articles and brochures for Hodges Gardens. Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material or subject.
      - Clippings, 1929-1964, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Exhibition Announcements, 1949-1950, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Exhibition Catalog, Milton Avery, 1947, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Exhibition Catalog, Jean Dubuffet, 1944-1960, undated (Box 32, Folder 14-15)
      - Exhibition Catalog, Hans Hofmann, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 16)
        Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 1.
      - Exhibition Catalog, Wassily Kandinsky, 1945-1956, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Exhibition Catalog, Loren MacIver, 1949-1961 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Exhibition Catalog, Piet Mondrian, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Exhibition Catalogs, Various, 1938-1960, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Greeting Cards, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)